A comedy on the edge.
Mixed Nuts is a comedy, drama, romance film directed by Nora Ephron.
The events of a crisis hotline business on one crazy
night during the Christmas holidays.
Philip, played by Steve Martin.
Blanche Munchnik, played by Madeline Kahn.
Catherine, played by Rita Wilson.
Gracie Barzini, played by Juliette Lewis.
Felix, played by Anthony LaPaglia.
Louie, played by Adam Sandler.
Mixed Nuts is a 1994 American Christmas black comedy film directed by Nora Ephron, based on the
1982 French comedy film Le Père Noël est une ordure (Santa Claus is a Stinker).
Co-written by Ephron and her sister Delia, the film features an ensemble cast which includes Steve Martin, Madeline Kahn, Rita
Wilson, Anthony LaPaglia, Garry Shandling, Rob Reiner, Juliette Lewis, Adam Sandler, and Liev Schreiber in his film debut.
The film was released theatrically on December 21, 1994, and
was both a critical and commercial failure.
The film explores themes of holiday, transvestite,
slapstick comedy, remake, rollerblades.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.